<resources>
    <string name="logo_description">logo</string>
    <string name="background_description">background</string>

    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="wave_now">Wave Now!</string>">

    <string name="events_select_all">All</string>
    <string name="events_select_starred">Starred</string>
    <string name="events_select_downloaded">Downloaded</string>

    <string name="events_uninstall_map_title">Uninstall Map</string>
    <string name="events_uninstall_map_confirmation">Are you sure you want to uninstall this map? You can download it again later if needed.</string>
    <string name="events_cannot_uninstall_map_message">This map cannot be uninstalled because it is part of the base app or is required by other features. It will be removed when you uninstall the app.</string>
    <string name="events_uninstall">Uninstall</string>
    <string name="events_uninstall_cancel">Cancel</string>

    <string name="event_done">Done</string>
    <string name="event_soon">soon !</string>
    <string name="event_running">running</string>
    <string name="event_favorite_on">favorite_on</string>
    <string name="event_favorite_off">favorite_off</string>

    <string name="event_target_wave_on">Target the wave</string>
    <string name="event_target_wave_off">The event is not running</string>
    <string name="event_target_me_on">Target me</string>
    <string name="event_target_me_off">You're not in the area</string>


    <string name="events_favorites_empty">No events has been added as favorite, start by clicking on the star icon on your favorite event!</string>
    <string name="events_downloaded_empty">No events has been yet downloaded</string>
    <string name="events_empty">Event list is empty</string>
    <string name="events_loading_error">An error occurred when loading events</string>

    <string name="map_checking_state">Checking map status</string>
    <string name="map_downloading">Downloading.. </string>
    <string name="map_starting_download">Starting download..</string>
    <string name="map_loading">Loading map..</string>
    <string name="map_cancel_download">Cancel</string>
    <string name="map_retry_download">Retry</string>
    <string name="map_error_download">Error downloading map</string>
    <string name="map_downloaded">Map has been downloaded</string>

    <string name="tab_infos_name">About</string>
    <string name="tab_faq_name">FAQ</string>

    <string name="geoloc_undone">Updating location..</string>
    <string name="geoloc_error">Unable to locate you</string>
    <string name="geoloc_yourein">YOU ARE in the area!</string>
    <string name="geoloc_yourenotin">YOU ARE NOT in the area</string>
    <string name="geoloc_warm_in">YOU ARE in the area and will warm!</string>
    <string name="geoloc_desc">FAQ</string>

    <string name="ask_gps_enable">Your GPS seems to be disabled, do you want to enable it?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>

    <string name="be_waved">be waved!</string>
    <string name="wave_speed">Wave speed</string>
    <string name="wave_start_time">Start time</string>
    <string name="wave_end_time">End time</string>
    <string name="wave_total_time">Total event time</string>
    <string name="wave_progression">Progression</string>

    <string name="wave_be_ready">Be ready!</string>
    <string name="wave_done">Wave is done!</string>
    <string name="wave_hit">Well done!</string>
    <string name="wave_is_running">Waving!</string>

    <string name="infos_core">
WorldWideWaves is an ephemeral mobile app with a visionary goal: to orchestrate a series of human waves that ripple through great cities, across countries, culminating in a final, awe-inspiring wave that spans the globe. Set to unfold over the span of one year, this initiative aims to transcend physical and cultural boundaries, fostering a sense of unity, community, and shared human experience.

At its core, WorldWideWaves is more than just an app—it's a global movement designed to bring people together in a display of solidarity and joy.

By leveraging technology, WorldWideWaves will enable participants from around the world to join in these human waves in their cities, creating a powerful visual and emotional spectacle.

In essence, WorldWideWaves is an ambitious endeavor to harness the power of technology for a truly noble cause—connecting humanity in a celebration of unity, joy and collective action. Through each wave, participants will not only contribute to a global spectacle but also experience the profound impact of coming together as one.
    </string>

    <string name="drwave">Dr Wave</string>
    <string name="drwave_instagram">@dr.wave</string>
    <string name="drwave_instagram_url">https://www.instagram.com/dr.wave/</string>
    <string name="www_instagram">@worldwide.waves</string>
    <string name="www_instagram_url">https://www.instagram.com/worldwide.waves/</string>
    <string name="www_hashtag">#wwwaves</string>

    <string name="warn_rules_security_title">Rules &amp; Security</string>
    <string name="warn_rules_security_text">Welcome to WorldWideWaves! We are excited to have you join our global wave events. To ensure everyone has a safe and enjoyable experience, please follow these guidelines:</string>
    <string name="warn_general_title">General Rules :</string>
    <string name="warn_general_item_1">Respect for All: Treat all participants with respect, regardless of their background. Please uphold respect for all attendees; discriminatory behavior or harassment is not acceptable at our events.</string>
    <string name="warn_general_item_2">Follow Directions: Adhere to instructions from event organizers and local authorities at all times if any.</string>
    <string name="warn_general_item_3">Stay Within Designated Areas: For your safety, remain within the areas designated for the event if any.</string>
    <string name="warn_general_item_4">No Alcohol or Illegal Substances: We kindly request that attendees refrain from bringing alcohol or illegal substances to the event.</string>
    <string name="warn_general_item_5">Minimize Environmental Impact: Dispose of all waste in designated receptacles and avoid littering to keep our venues clean.</string>
    <string name="warn_general_item_6">Report Concerns: If you see something suspicious or someone in distress, immediately report it to event staff or local authorities.</string>
    <string name="warn_safety_title">Safety Tips:</string>
    <string name="warn_safety_item_1">Dress Appropriately: Wear comfortable clothing and footwear suitable for the event's activities and weather conditions.</string>
    <string name="warn_safety_item_2">Stay Hydrated: Bring water and stay hydrated, especially during events in warm climates.</string>
    <string name="warn_safety_item_3">Be Mindful of Your Belongings: Keep personal belongings secure and avoid bringing valuables that you do not need.</string>
    <string name="warn_safety_item_4">Use the Buddy System: Stay with friends or make new ones, and look out for each other's safety.</string>
    <string name="warn_safety_item_5">First Aid: Familiarize yourself with the locations of first aid stations, which are clearly marked on the event map in the app.</string>
    <string name="warn_emergency_title">Emergency Procedures:</string>
    <string name="warn_emergency_item_1">Evacuation Routes: Know the evacuation routes, marked clearly in our app and at the event site.</string>
    <string name="warn_emergency_item_2">Emergency Contacts: Save the emergency contact numbers provided in the app, including local emergency services and event-specific contacts.</string>
    <string name="warn_emergency_item_3">In Case of Emergency: Follow the instructions of event staff and emergency responders. If an evacuation is ordered, leave promptly and calmly.</string>
    <string name="warn_legal_title">Legal:</string>
    <string name="warn_legal_item_1">Liability Waiver: Participation in WorldWideWaves events is at your own risk. By participating, you agree to waive any claims against the organizers related to injuries that could happen during the event.</string>
    <string name="warn_legal_item_2">Media Release: Events may be photographed or filmed for promotional purposes. Participation grants us permission to use your image in promotional materials.</string>

    <string name="faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="faq_access">Access FAQ</string>

    <string name="faq_question_1">Question 1</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_1">Answer 1</string>

    <string name="faq_question_2">Question 2</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_2">Answer 2</string>

    <string name="faq_question_3">Question 3</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_3">Answer 3</string>

    <string name="faq_question_4">Question 4</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_4">Answer 4</string>

    <string name="faq_question_5">Question 5</string>
    <string name="faq_answer_5">Answer 5</string>

</resources>